[Music]
which means this because you know from
their second I think the day is not far
we're not just the the answers but also
you know what the interaction they now
adjust things like how much time to give
the answer was there overnight or not
etc except a lot of interaction being I
would also start becoming a part of of
how you know responses are you guys like
you want to be sometimes I think the
cutting edge today is really you know
that maybe customized learning roadmaps
getting customized learning for students
based on they do not be based on their
own skills and where they are at this
point in time I think this is the area
to convene on right now and a lot of
successful startups are there in India
and also around the world and this is
truly the cutting edge right now where
you know as practitioners as
you think about how you can make more
customized learning roadmaps for the
students and what further people what
what I think the fun part data is that
you know you can always imagine how to
you fall in the future and what kind of
possibilities exist and you can easily
imagine that if things are going in a
vertically right now you can start
gathering locked up data on educational
outcomes and so you know a test outcome
versus an outcome in the in the in the
area of Education which is what would be
in the education outcomes and that we've
also correlated with professional
outcomes so this educational outcomes to
professional outcomes and they move
along Dominguez coming in and
essentially you know giving more
customized career advice or advice on
what their professions might make sense
what might make sense and and really
have a very customized experience for
the children for the students and what
people so I think that's where the field
is headed and you know and again it's on
all of us you know make it real you make
it but this kind of customized education
is where you're headed
and so think about it you know you know
twos will be a chemical engineer who's
will to be a you know
somebody died professional migrate
cetera so that's evolving so do you
think that you know customized roadmaps
such customized outcomes everything's
hunky-dory and you know it's all I think
there are a few questions which need to
be thrown into the mix here the first
part is really about mention about that
which is how does all of this lead to
you know what does it mean for the
people who are in the professionals
training so instead of learning instead
of jobs being you know generated because
what you know jobs are likely to be
given out based more based on what's
your flexibility wants to make that
ability and what's the ability to learn
even more skills because it's in fact
impossible that you know if you've been
training to a job for five years by the
end of five minutes that are over so how
does work pay the most flexibility
regarding to them and not more than what
you know but actually what do how you
solve problems and how you can think you
know generate solutions that's and the
second part about AI is that it's it's a
very powerful force but it's a
unidirectional force yeah I exchanged it
in so many problems right and banking is
all problems providing best customer
experience trying about the most
relevant offers you know in Vegas area
in song but it's a very directional port
and you know what the you know mystique
and the mystery of human mind I don't
think you know human mind falls into any
one bucket there are as many different
types of ways of learning many different
ways of of of you know gathering
intelligence for the human mind and so
one thing that we need to be careful
about this in you know efforts in our in
our efforts to get you need actual
excellence we should not lose anyone
behind or burst in any class of people
behind as they go for it more towards
targeted education so I think you know
that's you know that said you know he is
here he is very real and the is your
mistake which means that it's definitely
shaping educational outcomes here in
India and across the world and we
definitely avoid not just to us but also
to our future generations to make sure
that you know mean we mean provide this
these these kind of technologies to be
able to shape their